Guide to the Health Systems Agency of Southwestern Pennsylvania Records, 1971-1987 AIS.1987.02
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Projects, 1971-1987; I.
  - 247-Harmarville Rehabilitation Center--Planning for Rehabilitation of Cancer Patients, 1974
  - 248-Western Pennsylvania Regional Medical Program--Quality Assurance Program, 1974
  - 249-Allegheny Children and Youth Service Council--Coordination of Residential Care for Handicapped Children of Southwestern Pennsylvania, 1974
  - 250-Mercy and Children's Hospitals--Expand, Implement, and Evaluate the Drug Information Program of the Pharmaceutical Profile Center, 1974
  - 251-Columbia-Montour Home Health Services--Pennsylvania Assembly of Home Health Agencies Quality Assurance Project, 1974
  - 252-South Hills Health System, St. Joseph Division--South Hills Health System Primary Nursing Project, 1974
  - 253-St.Francis and Ellwood City Hospitals--Patient Evaluation Program, 1974
  - 254-Butler County Health and Welfare Council--Planning for the Delivery of Health Care in Butler County, 1974
  - 255-University of Pittsburgh School of Medicine, Department of Surgery--Comprehensive Public Information and Education Program for Renal Disease in Western Pennsylvania, 1974
  - 256-Presbyterian-University Hospital--Critical Care Nursing Education Program, 1974
  - 257-Allegheny General Hospital--Development of a Tumor Registry for Northwest Allegheny Hospital Corporation, 1974
  - 258-University of Pittsburgh School of Public Health, Department of Biostatistics--The Role of Aryl Hydrocarbon Hydroxylase in Lung Cancer among Coke Oven Workers, 1974
  - 259-Comprehensive Health Planning Association of Western Pennsylvania--Health Resources Data System, 1974
  - 260-Centerville Clinic--Centerville Clinic Community Mental Health Center, 1974
  - 261-Lawrence County Home--Addition of New Wing and Renovation of Existing Structure, 1974
  - 262-University of Pittsburgh School of Medicine--A Grant for the Planning and Early Implementation of a Comprehensive Regional Cancer Center, 1974
  - 263-Belair Nursing Home--Completion Proposal, 1974
  - 264-Connellsville State General Hospital--Critical Care Unit for Coronary and Intensive Care Patients, 1974
  - 265-Connellsville State General Hospital--Extended Care Unit at the Level of Skilled Nursing Care, 1974
  - 266-Beaver County Community College--Training Grant Application in Emergency Medical Services, 1974
  - 267-Community Medical Center of Northwestern Washington County--Construction of Primary Care Facility, 1974 (Box 104)
  - 268-University of Pittsburgh School of Pharmacy--Health Center Dial Access Medical and Drug Information Systems, 1974
  - 269-Children's Hospital of Pittsburgh--Regional Pediatric Program, 1974
  - 270-Indiana Hospital--Program for Development, 1974
  - 271-Pennsylvania Department of Health--Pennsylvania Coalworkers of Respiratory Disease Program, 1974
  - 272-Sugar Creek Rest Home--Proposal for Addition of Twenty-two Intermediate Care Beds, 1974
  - 273-Allegheny General Hospital--Planning and Development Prospectus (Phase II), 1974
  - 274-St. Margaret Memorial Hospital--Replacement of Obsolete Radiology Equipment, First Annual Report, 1974
  - 275-Pennsylvania Department of Health--Venereal Disease Control Continuation, 1974
  - 276-Human Services Center--Reapplication for Federal Assistance, 1974 (Box 104-105)
  - 277-Kiski Valley Visiting Nurses Association--Home Health Care Services for Armstrong County, 1974 (Box 105)
  - 278-Community Health Association--Application to Commence Operation of Prepaid Group Practice Health Delivery Program, 1974
  - 279-Western Pennsylvania Hospital--Equipment Replacement, 1974
  - 280-Magee-Women's Hospital--Acquisition of Parking Property, 1974
  - 281-Oakland Convalescent Center--Personal Health Service Proposal, 1974
  - 282-South Hills Health System--Construction of New Hospital and Renovation of Existing Facility, 1974
  - 283-Henry Clay Frick Community Hospital--Additions and Renovations, 1974
  - 284-Homewood-Brushton Neighborhood Health Center--Continuing Grant Application, 1974
  - 285-South Hills Health System--Community Mental Health/Mental Retardation Center Continuation Grant, 1974
  - 286-Fazio Nursing Home--74 Bed ICF Linked to the Nursing Home, 1974
  - 287-Mercy Hospital--Erection of Parking Garage, 1974
  - 288-Murray Manor Convalescent Center--Project Expansion Proposal, 1974
  - 289-not present
  - 290-Kiski Valley Medical Facility--Primary Care Center, 1974
  - 291-Armstrong County Health Center--125 Bed Long-Term Care Facility, 1974
  - 292-Bio-Medical Applications of Pittsburgh--Expansion of Artificial Kidney Center Located Within St. Francis Hospital, 1974 (Box 106)
  - 293-Allegheny General Hospital--Establishing a Chronic Hemodialysis Unit, 1974
  - 294-Presbyterian-University Hospital--Project to Replace and Update Existing Radiology Facilities, 1974
  - 295-Golden Hill Nursing Home--Addition of Fifty Intermediate Care Beds, 1974
  - 296-Canonsburg General Hospital--Two Emergency Psychiatric Beds, 1974
  - 297-Lutheran Welfare Concordia Home--Life Safety Codes Renovations, First and Fourth Annual Reports, 1975
  - 298-Indiana County Community Action Program--National Health Service Corps, 1974
  - 299-Homewood-Brushton Neighborhood Health Center--Continuation Grant Application for the Drug Rehabilitation Program, 1975
  - 300-The Methodist Home and Hospital for the Aged--Life Safety Code Requirements of the Pennsylvania Department of Labor and Industry, 1975
  - 301-Suburban General Hospital--X-ray Equipment Replacement, 1974
  - 302-Montefiore Hospital--Conversion of Nurses Residence into a Multi-Purpose Facility, 1974
  - 303-St.Anne Home for the Elderly--Renovations for Compliance with the Life Safety Codes, 1974
  - 304-University Health Center of Pittsburgh, Montefiore and Children's Hospital--Leasing of Two EMI Scanners, 1974
  - 305-St. Francis Hospital--St. Francis Community MH/MR Clinic Continuation Staffing Grant, 1974
  - 306-Westmoreland Hospital Association--Remodeling of Nursery, 1974
  - 307-Canonsburg General Hospital--Replacement of X-Ray Unit, 1974
  - 308-Twin Valley Convalescent Home--Renovations, 1974
  - 309-Washington and Jefferson College--Baccalaureate Degree Nursing Program, 1975
  - 310-not present
  - 311-Allegheny County Health Department--Federal Rodent Control Neighborhood Improvement Program Proposal, 1974
  - 312-Mid-Allegheny Clarion Valley Regional Health System--Rural Health Initiative Program, 1975
  - 313-Hoffman Memorial Medical Center--National Health Service Corps Application, 1974 (Box 107)
  - 314-Indiana County Community Action Program--Rural Health Initiative Program, 1975
  - 315-Board of Commissioners, Allegheny County--Emergency Medical Services Project Year III, 1975
  - 316-Holmes House--Holmes House Life Safety Proposal, 1975
  - 317-University of Pittsburgh--Cancer Control Program, 1975
  - 318-Irene Stacy Community Mental Health Center--Continuation of Federal Staffing, 1975
  - 319-Mercy Hospital--National Health Service Corps Continuation Application, 1975
  - 320-Uniontown Hospital--Phase II Building Program, 1975
  - 321-not present
  - 322-Butler County Memorial Hospital--Adolescent Inpatient Psychiatric Unit, 1975
  - 323-University of Pittsburgh School of Health Related Professions--Dietetics Program, 1975
  - 324-Allegheny General Hospital--Comprehensive Family and Child Care Program, 1975
  - 325-Allegheny County Health Department--Grant Renewal Application for Childhood Lead Poisoning Control Program, 1974
  - 326-Allegheny County Health Department--Continuation Application for Immunization Project, 1975
  - 327-Family Planning Council of Western Pennsylvania--Continuation Application, 1975
  - 328-Pine Hurst Nursing and Convalescent Home--New Facility, 1975
  - 329-Western State School and Hospital--Life Safety Code Corrections, 1975
  - 330-Latrobe Area Mental Health Center--Continuation Grant Application, 1975 (Box 108)
  - 331-Lions Community Health Center--Community Medical Center, 1975
  - 332-Westmoreland Hospital Community Mental Health Center--Continuation Staffing Grant, 1975
  - 333-Mayview State Hospital--Renovations to Meet Labor and Industry Life Safety Code Requirements, 1975
  - 334-Western Restoration Center--Renovations to Meet Labor and Industry Life Safety Code Requirements, 1975
  - 335-Kiski Valley Medical Facilities--Continuation Application, 1975
  - 336-Shadyside Hospital--Expansion of Intensive Care Facilities, Establishment of a Critical Care Medicine Program, 1975
  - 337-Mid-Monongahela Valley Council of Governments--Comprehensive Rodent Control Program, 1975
  - 338-University of Pittsburgh--Primary Care Program, 1975
  - 339-Cresson State School and Hospital--First Annual Report, 1976
  - 340-Emergency Medical Services Institute--Establishment and Initial Operation of an Emergency Medical Service for Southwestern Pennsylvania, 1975
  - 341-Dixmont State Hospital--Life Safety Code Renovation, 1975
  - 342-Westmoreland Hospital Association--Automated Computerized Tomographic Scanner, 1975
  - 343-Torrance State Hospital--Improvements to Meet Life Safety Code Requirements, 1975
  - 344-Ebensburg State School and Hospital--First Annual Report, 1976
  - 345-University of Pittsburgh--Adult Nurse Practitioner, 1974
  - 346-Presbyterian-University Hospital--Critical Care Nursing, 1974
  - 347-EACH--Quality Assurance Project, 1974
  - 348-Columbia-Montour Home Health Services--Pennsylvania Home Health Agencies, 1974
  - 349-Sewickley Valley Hospital--Beaver Valley Quality Assurance Program, 1974
  - 350-Pennsylvania Physical Therapy Association--Physical Therapy Quality Assurance Program, 1974
  - 351-Mercy Hospital and Children's Hospitals--Pharmaceutical Profile Center, 1974
  - 352-Western Pennsylvania Comprehensive Health Planning Agency--Health Resources Data System, 1974
  - 353-St. Francis and Ellwood City Hospitals--Lawrence County Patient Education, 1974
  - 354-Allegheny General Hospital--Pilot Tumor Registry, 1974
  - 355-Health and Welfare Planning Agency--Community-wide Health Education Program, 1975
  - 356-Braddock Hospital--Braddock Hospital Patient Education Program, 1975
  - 357-Mahoning Shenango Area Health Education Network--Continuation Grant Application, 1975 (Box 109)
  - 358-Allegheny Valley Hospital--Life Safety Code Renovations, 1975
  - 359-Mountain View Center--Long Term Care Facility, 1975
  - 360-Connellsville State General Hospital--Renovations for Life Safety Code, 1975
  - 361-St. Johns General Hospital--Development Plan/Program, 1975
  - 362-Western Pennsylvania Hospital--Long Range Plan and Development, 1975
  - 363-Citizen's General Hospital--Monitoring Equipment, 1975
  - 364-Westmoreland Hospital Association--Modernization and Expansion Program, 1975
  - 365-Aliquippa Hospital--Equipment, 1975
  - 366-University Health Center of Pittsburgh--Semi-Private Unit Renovation, 1975
  - 367-University Health Center of Pittsburgh--Remodeling of North Wing, 1975
  - 368-University Health Center of Pittsburgh--Seventh Floor Learning Center Expansion, 1975
  - 369-Divine Providence Hospital--Equipment Replacement, 1975
  - 370-Butler County Memorial Hospital--Nixon-Sarver Intermediate Care Facility, 1975
  - 371-Curry Memorial Home--Proposed Expansion, 1975
  - 372-Community Mental Health/Mental Retardation Center--Continuation Staffing Grant, 1975 (Box 110)
  - 373-Sudie Cameron Nursing Home--Renovations, 1975
  - 374-Fayette County Mental Health Clinic--Mental Health Outreach to Children and their Families Continuation Application, 1975
  - 375-Mercy Hospital--Acquisition of a Computerized Transaxial Tomography Unit, 1975
  - 376-Braddock General Hospital--Professional Office Building, 1975
  - 377-McKeesport Hospital--Establishment of Radiation Therapy Facility, 1975
  - 378-Connellsville State General Hospital--Proposal for Psychiatric Short-Term Inpatient Care, 1975
  - 379-not present
  - 380-Allegheny County Health Department--Maternity and Infant Care Project Renewal, 1975
  - 381-Homewood-Brushton Neighborhood Health Center--Continuation Grant Application, 1975
  - 382-Evergreen Convalescent Home--Life Safety Code Renovations, 1975
  - 383-South Hills Health System--Community Mental Health Center Continuation Grant, 1975
  - 384-Citizen's General Hospital--Life Safety Code Renovations, 1975
  - 385-The Washington Hospital--Additions and Remodeling, 1975
  - 386-not present
  - 387-University of Pittsburgh School of Health Related Professions--Application for a Grant to Assist in the Education and Training of Clinical and Community Dietitians, 1975
  - 388-Bonetti Convalescent Home--Addition of Sixty Skilled Beds, 1975
  - 389-West Penn Home Health Agency--Home Health Care, 1975
  - 390-Professional Home Health Agency--Development of Home Health Services, 1975 (Box 111)
  - 391-St. Francis General Hospital--Part F Community Mental Health Center Grant Continuation, 1975
  - 392-not present
  - 393-not present
  - 394-Mahoning Medical Center--New Primary Care Center, 1975
  - 395-Monongahela Valley Hospital--Construction of an Acute Care Hospital, 1975
  - 396-not present
  - 397-not present
  - 398-Allegheny Valley Hospital--Life Safety Code Construction, 1975
  - 399-Presbyterian Association for Care of the Aged and Orphans--Life Safety Code Renovations, 1975
  - 400-St. John's General Hospital--Life Safety Code Renovations, Expansion of Long-Term Care Facility, 1975
  - 401-Suburban General Hospital--Equipment Replacement, 1975
  - 402-Mon Valley Health and Welfare Authority--Expansion and Renovation of Physical Plant, 1975
  - 403-North Hills Passavant Hospital--Relocation of Department of Respiratory Care and Expansion of the Department of Radiology, 1975
  - 404-University Health Center of Pittsburgh--Human Vestibular Systems Laboratory, 1975
  - 405-Veterans Administration Hospital of Pittsburgh--CAT Scanner, 1975
  - 406-Shadyside Hospital--CAT Scanner, 1975
  - 407-Uniontown Hospital Association--Renovation for Relocating of Coffee-Gift Shop, 1975
  - 408-Baptist Homes--Life Safety Code Renovations, 1975 (Box 112)
  - 409-The Washington Hospital--Land Acquisition, 1976
  - 410-not present
  - 411-not present
  - 412-not present
  - 413-Kiski Valley Medical Facilities--Renovation of Primary Care Center, 1976
  - 414-Sunny Crest Convalescent Home--Expansion and Renovation, 1976
  - 415-Westmoreland Hospital--Community Mental Health Center Continuation Grant, 1976
  - 416-St. Margaret Memorial Hospital--New Facility, 1976
  - 417-Comprehensive Health Planning Council of the Southern Alleghenies--Application for Health Systems Agency Designation and Grant, 1976 (Box 113)
  - 418-Health Systems Agency of Southwestern Pennsylvania--Application for Designation as the Health Systems Agency of Southwestern Pennsylvania, 1976
  - 419-Irene Stacy Community Mental Health Center--Continuation of Federal Staffing Grant, 1976
  - 420-Jameson Memorial Hospital--Air Conditioning and Air Handling Renovation and Remodeling, 1976
  - 421-Allegheny County Health Department--Continuation Application for the Immunization Project, 1976
  - 422-Fayette County Mental Health Outreach to Children and Their Families--Federal Staffing Grant Continuation, 1976
  - 423-Woodville State Hospital--Evaluation and Placement of Geriatric Patients, 1976
  - 424-Mid-Allegheny Clarion Valley Regional Health System--Rural Health Initiative Program Continuation, 1976
  - 425-Kiski Valley Medical Facilities--Continuation Application for a Second Year, 1976
  - 426-not present
  - 427-St. Francis General Hospital--Modernization of North Wing, 1976
  - 428-Latrobe Area Mental Health Center--Continuation Staffing Grant, 1976
  - 429-Indiana Hospital--Expansion and Renovation, 1976
  - 430-not present
  - 431-Regional Comprehensive Rehabilitation Center for Children and Youth--Remodeling Outpatient Facilities, 1976
  - 432-Kiski Valley Medical Facilities--Comprehensive Dental Care Clinic, 1976 (Box 114)
  - 433-Centerville Clinic--Application for Community Mental Health Center Consultation and Education Grant, 1976
  - 434- South Hills Health System Community Mental Health/Mental Retardation Center--NIMH Staffing Grant, 1976
  - 435-South Hills Health System--Preventative Service for Children Grant Continuation, 1976
  - 436-South Hills Health Center Community Mental Health/Mental Retardation Center--Consultation and Education Grant Continuation, 1976
  - 437-not present
  - 438-Armstrong/Indiana Mental Health/Mental Retardation Program--Application for Community Mental Health Center Planning Grant, 1976
  - 439-Westmoreland Hospital Association--Westmoreland Hospital Community Mental Health Center Supplemental Funding Grant Application, 1976
  - 440-Southwest Pittsburgh Mental Health/Mental Retardation Program--Application for Initial Operations Grant, 1976
  - 441-Family Planning Council of Western Pennsylvania--Year Six Continuation Application, 1976
  - 442-University Health Center-Children's Hospital--Tomography Equipment Replacement, 1976
  - 443-Allegheny General Hospital--Revised Construction Plan, 1976
  - 444-Latrobe Area Mental Health Center--Consultation and Education Grant, 1976
  - 445-Pennsylvania Department of Health--Communicable Disease Control in Pennsylvania Continuation Grant Application, 1976
  - 446-Mayview State Hospital-Relocation of Children's Psychiatric Treatment Service from Western State School and Hospital, 1976
  - 447-St. Joseph Home for the Aged--Life Safety Code Renovation and Addition of 47 Beds, 1976
  - 448-Pennsylvania Department of Health--Venereal Disease Control Continuation Application, 1976
  - 449-not present
  - 450-Allegheny Valley Hospital--Replacement of Angiographic Equipment, 1976
  - 451-Emergency Medical Services Institute--Proposal for the Establishment and Initial Operation of an Emergency Medical Services System, 1976 (Box 115)
  - 452-University Health Center of Pittsburgh-Children's Hospital--Surgical Facility Expansion, 1976
  - 453-not present
  - 454-not present
  - 455-Wexford House-Expansion, 1976
  - 456-Allegheny County Health Department--Allegheny County Influenza Immunization Project, 1976
  - 457-McKeesport Hospital--Nuclear Equipment Replacement, 1976
  - 458-Pennsylvania Department of Health--Influenza Immunization Activities Grant, 1976
  - 459-Armstrong County Health Center--Addition of 31 Bed Skilled and Intermediate Care Beds, 1976
  - 460-Chicora Medical Center--Addition of 26 Skilled Care Beds, 1976
  - 461-Presbyterian Association for Care of Aged and Orphans--Life Safety Code Renovations, 1976
  - 462-not present
  - 463-not present
  - 464-Aliquippa Hospital--Modernization and Expansion of Support Service Areas, 1976 (Box 116)
  - 465-North Hills Passavant Hospital--Computerized Axial Tomography Scanner, 1976
  - 466-Department of Community Affairs--Development and Operational Plan for the Establishment of Health Maintenance Organizations in Pennsylvania Communities, 1976
  - 467-Chronic Respiratory and Occupational Disease Services--Intensive Control of Tuberculosis, 1976
  - 468-Central Medical Health Services--Sprinkler System, 1976
  - 469-Central Medical Health Services--Cardiac Catheterization Unit, 1976
  - 470-Homewood-Brushton Neighborhood Health Center--Community Health Services Project Grant Application, 1976
  - 471-Windsor House Convalescent Home--New Facility, 1976
  - 472-University Health Center--Joint Radiation Oncology Center, 1976
  - 473-Jeanette District Memorial Hospital--Life Safety Code Renovations, 1976
  - 474-Forbes Health Center--Proposal for East Suburban Health Center, 1976 (Box 116-117)
  - 475-499-not present
  - 500-McKeesport Hospital--Biochemical Analyzer, 1976 (Box 118)
  - 501-Butler County Memorial Hospital--Life Safety Code Renovations, 1976
  - 502-St. Francis General Hospital--Continuation Staffing Grant Application for Community Mental Health/Mental Retardation Center, 1976
  - 503-Forbes Health Center--Columbia Health Center Radiology Application, 1976
  - 504-Armsdale Home and Hospital--Addition of 118 Bed Facility, 1976
  - 505-Suburban General Hospital--Radiology Equipment, 1976
  - 506-Divine Providence Hospital--Dietary Department Renovation, 1976
  - 507-St. John's General Hospital--Plan/Program for Development, 1976
  - 508-University Health Center of Pittsburgh-Children's Hospital--CT Scanner, 1876
  - 509-Allegheny County Health Department--Year 4 of Rodent Control Program, 1977
  - 510-Mercy Hospital--CAT Scanner, 1977
  - 511-St. Francis General Hospital--Air Conditioning Unit, 1977 (Box 119)
  - 512-Aliquippa Hospital--Life Safety Code Renovations, 1977
  - 513-North Hills Passavant Hospital--Expansion of Hospital Building, 1977
  - 514-Sunnyview Home--180 Bed Addition, 1977
  - 515-Forbes Health System-Columbia Health Center--Life Safety Code Renovations, 1977
  - 516-Graham's Nursing Home--Renovation and Expansion, 1977
  - 517-Presbyterian University Hospital--Life Safety Code Renovations, 1977
  - 518-Ohio Valley Hospital--Project Changes, 1977
  - 519-Medical Center of Beaver County-Rochester Unit--Radiology Equipment, 1977
  - 520-Medical Center of Beaver County-Beaver Falls Unit--Radiology Equipment, 1977
  - 521-Jefferson Hills Nursing Home--50 Bed Addition, 1977
  - 522-Irene Stacy Community Mental Health Center--Federal Staffing Grant Continuation Application, 1977 (Box 120)
  - 523-St. Margaret Memorial Hospital--Development of the Primary Care Group Practice in West Deer Township, 1977
  - 524-Family Counseling Center of Armstrong County--Outpatient Services, 1977
  - 525-Southern Indiana Health System--Development of a Primary Care Health Center, 1977
  - 526-Bio-Medical Applications of Southwestern Pennsylvania--Establishment of a Ten Station Hemodialysis Facility, 1977
  - 527-Sugar Creek Rest Home--Sixty LTC Bed Addition, 1977-1978
  - 528-St. Joseph Home for the Aged--Renovation of Fourth Floor with an Addition of Fifty Skilled Beds, 1977
  - 529-Fobes Health System--Penn Hills Primary Care Unit, 1977
  - 530-Butler Alcoholism Recover Center--Grant Application for a Female Alcoholic Program, 1977
  - 531-Allegheny County Health Department--Mobile Environmental Education Unit, 1977 (Box 121)
  - 532-Westmoreland Hospital Community Mental Health Center--Continuation Staffing Grant Application, 1977
  - 533-Canonsburg General Hospital--X-ray Unit Replacement, 1977
  - 534-South Hills Health System-Community Mental Health/Mental Retardation Center--Consultation and Education Grant, 1977
  - 535-Latrobe Area Mental Health Center--Community Mental Health Center Staffing Continuation Grant Application, 1977
  - 536-Magee Women's Hospital--Conversion of Gynecological Surgery Unit to Obstetrical Unit and Nursery, 1977
  - 537-Presbyterian University Hospital--Urology Suite, Financial Statements, 1977
  - 538-Eye and Ear Hospital--Diagnostic Radiology Facility, 1977
  - 539-University Health Center of Pittsburgh-Falk Clinic--Ambulatory Care Module, 1977
  - 540-Forbes Health System--Inhouse Computer Service Proposal, 1977
  - 541-Butler County Memorial Hospital--Nuclear Medicine Equipment, 1977
  - 542-Mt. Lebanon Manor Convalescent Center--New Facility, 1977
  - 543-Centerville Clinic Community Mental Health Center--Continuation Staffing Grant, 1977 (Box 122)
  - 544-not present
  - 545-Aliquippa Hospital--Renovation and Modernization, 1977
  - 546-Westmoreland Hospital--Upgrade ACTA Scanner, 1977
  - 547-Woodville State Hospital--Evaluation and Placement of Geriatric Patients, Third Year Renewal Application, 1977
  - 548-Mid-Allegheny Clarion Valley Regional Health System--Continuation Application for Financial Assistance, 1977
  - 549-Emergency Medical Service Institute--Grant for EMS Training, 1977
  - 550-The Community Medical Center of Northwest Washington County--Application for Funding for Primary Care Delivery System, 1977